import { INTF_HomeWork } from '../../Interface/HomeWork/HomeWork';

const Beginner: INTF_HomeWork[] = [
    // Lesson ID: 101
    {
        lesson_id: 101,
        question: 'Which type of words describe or modify nouns?',
        options: ['Verbs', 'Adjectives', 'Adverbs', 'Prepositions'],
        answer: 'Adjectives',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 101,
        question: 'How do you form comparatives of adjectives?',
        options: [
            'By adding -er',
            'By adding -est',
            'By adding -ier',
            'By adding more',
        ],
        answer: 'By adding -er',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 101,
        question: 'What is the superlative form of adjectives?',
        options: [
            'By adding -est',
            'By adding -er',
            'By adding -iest',
            'By adding the most',
        ],
        answer: 'By adding -est',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 101,
        question: 'Which type of words describe or modify verbs?',
        options: ['Adjectives', 'Adverbs', 'Nouns', 'Pronouns'],
        answer: 'Adverbs',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 101,
        question: "Which word order is correct? 'She sings ____.'",
        options: ['Good', 'Well', 'Quick', 'Quickly'],
        answer: 'Well',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 102
    {
        lesson_id: 102,
        question:
            'Which article is used before words starting with a consonant sound?',
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', '0 article'],
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 102,
        question: 'What is the superlative form of adjectives?',
        options: [
            'The best',
            'The most interesting',
            'The better',
            'The most good',
        ],
        answer: 'The best',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 102,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I have ____ apple.'",
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', '0 article'],
        answer: 'An',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 102,
        question: "Choose the correct article: 'She has ____ book.'",
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', '0 article'],
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 102,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I feel ____ love.'",
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', '0 article'],
        answer: '0 article',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 103
    {
        lesson_id: 103,
        question: 'Which conditional is used to talk about general truths?',
        options: [
            'First conditional',
            'Second conditional',
            'Third conditional',
            'Zero conditional',
        ],
        answer: 'Zero conditional',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 103,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conditional: 'If it rains, I ____ an umbrella.'",
        options: ['Will take', 'Would take', 'Took', 'Take'],
        answer: 'Will take',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 103,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: 'If you study hard, you ____ good grades.'",
        options: ['Get', 'Got', 'Will get', 'Would get'],
        answer: 'Will get',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 103,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conditional: 'If I had money, I ____ a car.'",
        options: ['Buy', 'Bought', 'Will buy', 'Would buy'],
        answer: 'Would buy',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 103,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'If he calls, ____ him a message.'",
        options: ['Leaving', 'Leave', 'Left', 'To leave'],
        answer: 'Leave',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 104
    {
        lesson_id: 104,
        question: 'Which tense is used to talk about sudden decisions?',
        options: [
            'Past simple',
            'Present perfect',
            'Future with will',
            'Future with going to',
        ],
        answer: 'Future with will',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 104,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ see my sister for Christmas.'",
        options: ['Will', 'Am', 'Going to', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Am',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 104,
        question:
            "Choose the correct question form: '____ you carry my bag, please?'",
        options: ['Will', 'Do', 'Are', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Will',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 104,
        question: "Choose the correct verb form: 'I ____ you with that.'",
        options: ['Will help', 'Helped', 'Help', 'Helping'],
        answer: 'Will help',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 104,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ to see a film yesterday.'",
        options: ['Visited', 'Will visit', 'Visiting', 'Visit'],
        answer: 'Visited',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 105
    {
        lesson_id: 105,
        question: 'Which verbs are followed by infinitives or gerunds?',
        options: [
            'Action verbs',
            'Stative verbs',
            'Modal verbs',
            'Irregular verbs',
        ],
        answer: 'Action verbs',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 105,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'I like ____.'",
        options: ['Reading', 'To read', 'Reads', 'Read'],
        answer: 'Reading',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 105,
        question: "Which verb is stative? 'I ____ to the beach.'",
        options: ['Go', 'Am going', 'Goes', 'Went'],
        answer: 'Go',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 105,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I want ____ my family.'",
        options: ['To see', 'Seeing', 'See', 'Saw'],
        answer: 'To see',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 105,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'She loves ____.'",
        options: ['Singing', 'To sing', 'Sings', 'Sang'],
        answer: 'Singing',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 106
    {
        lesson_id: 106,
        question: 'Which tense is used to talk about actions in the past?',
        options: [
            'Past simple',
            'Present perfect',
            'Past continuous',
            'Past perfect',
        ],
        answer: 'Past simple',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 106,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form of 'to be' in the past simple: 'I ____ at home.'",
        options: ['Am', 'Were', 'Was', 'Is'],
        answer: 'Was',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 106,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ to see a film yesterday.'",
        options: ['Went', 'Go', 'Goes', 'Will go'],
        answer: 'Went',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 106,
        question: "Choose the correct verb form: 'I ____ last night.'",
        options: ['Work', 'Working', 'Works', 'Worked'],
        answer: 'Worked',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 106,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I didnâ€™t ____.'",
        options: ['Work', 'Working', 'Works', 'Worked'],
        answer: 'Work',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 107
    {
        lesson_id: 107,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used for abilities?',
        options: ['Can', 'Could', 'Must', 'Should'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 107,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'I ____ swim.'",
        options: ['Can', 'Could', "Can't", "Couldn't"],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 107,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ swim when I was five.'",
        options: ['Could', 'Can', "Couldn't", "Can't"],
        answer: 'Could',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 107,
        question:
            "Choose the correct question form: '____ you help me to find the purse?'",
        options: ['Could', 'Can', 'Will', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Could',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 107,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'You ____ smoke around children.'",
        options: ["Mustn't", "Shouldn't", "Can't", "Needn't"],
        answer: "Mustn't",
    },
    // Lesson ID: 108
    {
        lesson_id: 108,
        question: 'Which preposition is used to show location?',
        options: ['At', 'Of', 'By', 'Into'],
        answer: 'At',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 108,
        question:
            "Choose the correct preposition: 'The book is ____ the table.'",
        options: ['At', 'On', 'In', 'By'],
        answer: 'On',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 108,
        question:
            "Choose the correct preposition: 'The cat is ____ the table and the chair.'",
        options: ['Among', 'Between', 'Beside', 'Next to'],
        answer: 'Between',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 108,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'She walked ____ the room.'",
        options: ['Across', 'Into', 'By', 'Through'],
        answer: 'Across',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 108,
        question: "Choose the correct preposition: 'He jumped ____ the river.'",
        options: ['Into', 'By', 'Under', 'Next to'],
        answer: 'Into',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 109
    {
        lesson_id: 109,
        question:
            'Which pronouns are used to replace specific people or things?',
        options: [
            'Personal pronouns',
            'Possessive pronouns',
            'Object pronouns',
            'Demonstrative pronouns',
        ],
        answer: 'Personal pronouns',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 109,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'This is ____ house.'",
        options: ['My', 'Your', 'His', 'Her'],
        answer: 'My',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 109,
        question: "Choose the correct pronoun: '____ are my friends.'",
        options: ['We', 'They', 'I', 'You'],
        answer: 'They',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 109,
        question: "Choose the correct pronoun: 'She is talking to ____.'",
        options: ['Me', 'You', 'Him', 'Her'],
        answer: 'Me',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 109,
        question: "Complete the sentence: '____ is a good student.'",
        options: ['He', 'She', 'I', 'It'],
        answer: 'He',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 110
    {
        lesson_id: 110,
        question: 'Which conjunction is used to show addition?',
        options: ['And', 'But', 'Or', 'So'],
        answer: 'And',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 110,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conjunction: 'I like coffee, ____ I don't drink it often.'",
        options: ['And', 'But', 'Or', 'So'],
        answer: 'But',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 110,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: 'He can play ____ the piano ____ the guitar.'",
        options: [
            'Either, or',
            'Neither, nor',
            'Both, and',
            'Not only, but also',
        ],
        answer: 'Both, and',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 110,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conjunction: 'I will come ____ you study.'",
        options: ['If', 'Because', 'While', 'When'],
        answer: 'If',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 110,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: 'She is tall ____ she is also very athletic.'",
        options: ['But', 'So', 'And', 'Or'],
        answer: 'And',
    },
];

const PreIntermediate: INTF_HomeWork[] = [
    // Lesson ID: 201
    {
        lesson_id: 201,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'She sings ____.'",
        options: ['Good', 'Well', 'Better', 'Best'],
        answer: 'Well',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 201,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'He runs ____.'",
        options: ['Fast', 'Faster', 'Fastest', 'More fast'],
        answer: 'Fast',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 201,
        question: "Choose the correct adjective: 'The movie was ____.'",
        options: ['Sudden', 'Suddenest', 'Suddenly', 'Suddenest'],
        answer: 'Sudden',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 201,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form: 'This is the ____ book I have ever read.'",
        options: ['Good', 'Better', 'Best', 'Gooder'],
        answer: 'Best',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 201,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'He plays the guitar ____ than me.'",
        options: ['Good', 'Better', 'Best', 'Gooder'],
        answer: 'Better',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 202
    {
        lesson_id: 202,
        question: "Choose the correct article: 'I saw ____ cat in the garden.'",
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', 'No article'],
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 202,
        question:
            "Choose the correct article: 'Can you pass me ____ salt, please?'",
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', 'No article'],
        answer: 'The',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 202,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'She is ____ student in the class.'",
        options: ['Good', 'Better', 'The best', 'Gooder'],
        answer: 'The best',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 202,
        question: "Choose the correct article: 'I want to buy ____ new car.'",
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', 'No article'],
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 202,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'He is ____ person I've ever met.'",
        options: ['Good', 'Better', 'The best', 'Gooder'],
        answer: 'The best',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 203
    {
        lesson_id: 203,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'If it rains, I ____ my umbrella.'",
        options: ['Take', 'Took', 'Will take', 'Would take'],
        answer: 'Will take',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 203,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I will come ____ you cancel.'",
        options: ['If', 'Unless', 'Although', 'Since'],
        answer: 'Unless',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 203,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'If only my boyfriend ____.'",
        options: ['Knew', 'Knows', 'Will know', 'Would know'],
        answer: 'Knew',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 203,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I wish I ____ taller.'",
        options: ['Am', 'Was', 'Were', 'Will be'],
        answer: 'Was',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 203,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I wish it ____ true.'",
        options: ['Is', 'Was', 'Were', 'Will be'],
        answer: 'Was',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 204
    {
        lesson_id: 204,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conjunction: 'I went out ____ it was raining.'",
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Why'],
        answer: 'When',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 204,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: 'She is the woman ____ can speak five languages.'",
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Who'],
        answer: 'Who',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 204,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conjunction: 'Emma lives in a house ____ is 100 years old.'",
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'That'],
        answer: 'That',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 204,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conjunction: 'Tell me ____ you want to go.'",
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Why'],
        answer: 'Why',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 204,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'This is the place ____ I was born.'",
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Why'],
        answer: 'Where',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 205
    {
        lesson_id: 205,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form: 'I ____ show you how to use the new laptop.'",
        options: ['Will', 'Am', 'Going to', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Will',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 205,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'Sarah ____ sell her car.'",
        options: ['Will', 'Am', 'Going to', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Is going to',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 205,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'The plane ____ at 8.'",
        options: ['Leaves', 'Will leave', 'Is leaving', 'Left'],
        answer: 'Leaves',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 205,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'He ____ working tomorrow.'",
        options: [
            'Is not working',
            'Will not work',
            "Doesn't work",
            "Didn't work",
        ],
        answer: 'Is not working',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 205,
        question: "Choose the correct form: '____ you do it for me?'",
        options: ['Will', 'Can', 'Could', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Will',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 206
    {
        lesson_id: 206,
        question: "Choose the correct verb: 'They decided ____ to the party.'",
        options: ['Go', 'To go', 'Going', 'Gone'],
        answer: 'To go',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 206,
        question: "Choose the correct verb: 'I prefer ____ at home.'",
        options: ['Stay', 'To stay', 'Staying', 'Stayed'],
        answer: 'To stay',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 206,
        question: "Choose the correct verb: 'I hope ____ the concert.'",
        options: ['Attend', 'To attend', 'Attending', 'Attended'],
        answer: 'To attend',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 206,
        question: "Choose the correct verb: 'She forgot ____ the milk.'",
        options: ['Buy', 'To buy', 'Buying', 'Bought'],
        answer: 'To buy',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 207
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ play tennis.'",
        options: ['Can', "Can't", 'Could', "Couldn't"],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: 'She ____ paint before she started school.'",
        options: ['Could', "Couldn't", 'Can', "Can't"],
        answer: 'Could',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: '____ you post this letter for me?'",
        options: ['Could', 'Can', 'Should', 'Must'],
        answer: 'Could',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I must ____ clean.'",
        options: ['Be', 'Been', 'Have', 'Do'],
        answer: 'Clean',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I mustn't ____ late.'",
        options: ['Am', 'Be', 'Being', 'Been'],
        answer: 'Be',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'You need to ____.'",
        options: ['Study', 'Studying', 'Studied', 'Studies'],
        answer: 'Study',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'You needn't ____ yet.'",
        options: ['Go', 'Going', 'Went', 'Gone'],
        answer: 'Go',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'You needn't wear ____.'",
        options: ['Glass', 'Glasses', 'A glass', 'The glasses'],
        answer: 'Glasses',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: '____ I leave now?'",
        options: ['Can', 'May', 'Should', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: '____ I open that door, please?'",
        options: ['Can', 'May', 'Should', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: '____ we see your parents next week?'",
        options: ['Can', 'May', 'Shall', 'Would'],
        answer: 'Shall',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'You should ____ more.'",
        options: ['Sleep', 'Sleeps', 'Sleeping', 'Slept'],
        answer: 'Sleep',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 207,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'You shouldn't ____ so much.'",
        options: ['Work', 'Working', 'Worked', 'Works'],
        answer: 'Work',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 208
    {
        lesson_id: 208,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ last night.'",
        options: ['Worked', "Didn't work", 'Did work', "Hadn't work"],
        answer: "Didn't work",
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 208,
        question: "Complete the sentence: '____ you go to the party?'",
        options: ['Did', "Didn't", 'Do', 'Does'],
        answer: 'Did',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 208,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'She ____ her homework.'",
        options: ['Did', "Didn't", 'Do', 'Does'],
        answer: "Didn't",
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 208,
        question: "Complete the sentence: '____ they study yesterday?'",
        options: ['Did', "Didn't", 'Do', 'Does'],
        answer: 'Did',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 208,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ a great time at the party.'",
        options: ['Had', "Hadn't", 'Have', "Haven't"],
        answer: 'Had',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 209
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'She can ____ the guitar.'",
        options: ['Play', 'Plays', 'Playing', 'Played'],
        answer: 'Play',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: '____ he like ice cream?'",
        options: ['Do', 'Does', 'Did', 'Doing'],
        answer: 'Does',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: '____ they live in London?'",
        options: ['Do', 'Does', 'Did', 'Doing'],
        answer: 'Do',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: 'He ____ the piano.'",
        options: ['Play', 'Plays', 'Playing', 'Played'],
        answer: 'Plays',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: '____ you like pizza?'",
        options: ['Do', 'Does', 'Did', 'Doing'],
        answer: 'Do',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: '____ I have a coffee?'",
        options: ['Do', 'Does', 'Did', 'Doing'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: '____ she go to school by bus?'",
        options: ['Do', 'Does', 'Did', 'Doing'],
        answer: 'Does',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 209,
        question: "Choose the correct form: '____ they speak Spanish?'",
        options: ['Do', 'Does', 'Did', 'Doing'],
        answer: 'Do',
    },
    // Lesson ID: 210
    {
        lesson_id: 210,
        question:
            "Complete the sentence: 'She ____ to the beach every summer.'",
        options: ['Goes', 'Go', 'Going', 'Went'],
        answer: 'Goes',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 210,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'We ____ dinner at 7.'",
        options: ['Has', 'Have', 'Having', 'Had'],
        answer: 'Have',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 210,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'He ____ his homework every day.'",
        options: ['Does', 'Do', 'Doing', 'Did'],
        answer: 'Does',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 210,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ____ English at school.'",
        options: ['Studied', 'Study', 'Studying', 'Studies'],
        answer: 'Study',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 210,
        question: "Complete the sentence: 'They ____ football every weekend.'",
        options: ['Plays', 'Play', 'Playing', 'Played'],
        answer: 'Play',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 211,
        question: "Choose the correct personal pronoun: '____ is my friend.'",
        options: ['I', 'He', 'She', 'They'],
        answer: 'He',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 211,
        question: "Choose the correct possessive pronoun: 'This book is ____.'",
        options: ['My', 'Her', 'Your', 'Their'],
        answer: 'My',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 211,
        question: "Choose the correct object pronoun: 'She gave ____ a gift.'",
        options: ['I', 'Me', 'You', 'Her'],
        answer: 'Me',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 211,
        question:
            "Choose the correct demonstrative pronoun: '____ is my favorite color.'",
        options: ['That', 'Those', 'This', 'These'],
        answer: 'This',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 211,
        question: "Choose the correct pronoun: 'I don't know ____.'",
        options: ['Something', 'Anything', 'Everything', 'Nothing'],
        answer: 'Anything',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 211,
        question:
            "Choose the correct reflexive pronoun: 'She bought the dress for ____.'",
        options: ['Myself', 'Herself', 'Yourself', 'Themselves'],
        answer: 'Herself',
    },
];

const Intermediate: INTF_HomeWork[] = [
    // Adjectives and Adverbs
    {
        lesson_id: 301,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: She was ____ after the long journey. (tired/tiring)',
        options: ['tired', 'tiring'],
        answer: 'tired',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 301,
        question:
            'Choose the correct adverb: I ____ go to the gym. (always/never)',
        options: ['always', 'never'],
        answer: 'never',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 301,
        question:
            'Choose the correct word order: They ____ late. (are/never/I)',
        options: ['are', 'never', 'I'],
        answer: 'are',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 301,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form of the adjective: This is ____ book I've ever read. (little/less/the least)",
        options: ['little', 'less', 'the least'],
        answer: 'the least',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 301,
        question:
            "Choose the correct phrase: Laura gets ____ salary as me. (the same/same/you're just the same)",
        options: ['the same', 'same', "you're just the same"],
        answer: 'the same',
    },
    // Conditionals
    {
        lesson_id: 302,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: If people eat too much, ____.',
        options: [
            'they get fat quickly',
            'they will get fat quickly',
            'they got fat quickly',
        ],
        answer: 'they get fat quickly',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 302,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: If you are late, ____.',
        options: ['I will be angry', 'I would be angry', 'I am angry'],
        answer: 'I will be angry',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 302,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: If they had time, ____.',
        options: [
            'they will go on holiday',
            'they would go on holiday',
            'they go on holiday',
        ],
        answer: 'they would go on holiday',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 302,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: We would have won if ____.',
        options: [
            'we play better',
            'we had played better',
            'we will play better',
        ],
        answer: 'we had played better',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 302,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: If it rains, ____.',
        options: [
            'I take an umbrella',
            'I took an umbrella',
            'I will take an umbrella',
        ],
        answer: 'I will take an umbrella',
    },
    // Conjunctions
    {
        lesson_id: 303,
        question:
            'Choose the correct conjunction: He will come ____ I invite him.',
        options: ['if', 'unless', 'until'],
        answer: 'if',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 303,
        question:
            'Choose the correct conjunction: I will wait here ____ you come back.',
        options: ['since', 'while', 'until'],
        answer: 'until',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 303,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conjunction: She didn't know ____ she should do it.",
        options: ['what', 'when', 'why'],
        answer: 'what',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 303,
        question:
            "Choose the correct conjunction: He can't play ____ he practices more.",
        options: ['before', 'as', 'after'],
        answer: 'unless',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 303,
        question:
            'Choose the correct conjunction: I always take an umbrella ____ it rains.',
        options: ['since', 'as', 'whenever'],
        answer: 'if',
    },

    // Future Tenses
    {
        lesson_id: 304,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: We ____ ask for directions if we get lost.',
        options: ['can', 'may', 'should'],
        answer: 'should',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 304,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: By this time next year, he ____ his degree.',
        options: ['will have', 'will', 'is going to have'],
        answer: 'will have',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 304,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: She ____ the laundry this afternoon.',
        options: ['is going to do', 'will do', 'does'],
        answer: 'is going to do',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 304,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: They ____ to the beach if the weather is nice.',
        options: ['will go', 'go', 'are going to go'],
        answer: 'will go',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 304,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: We ____ dinner by the time you arrive.',
        options: ['will have finished', 'finish', 'are going to finish'],
        answer: 'will have finished',
    },

    // Gerund and Infinitive
    {
        lesson_id: 305,
        question:
            'Choose the verb followed by the infinitive: He offered ____ help.',
        options: ['to', 'that', 'for'],
        answer: 'to',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 305,
        question:
            "Choose the verb followed by the gerund: We can't imagine ____ without her.",
        options: ['to live', 'living', 'live'],
        answer: 'living',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 305,
        question:
            'Choose the verb that can be followed by both the infinitive and gerund: She started ____ guitar lessons.',
        options: ['to take', 'taking', 'take'],
        answer: 'taking',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 305,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form: I prefer ____ at home rather than going out.',
        options: ['to stay', 'staying', 'stay'],
        answer: 'staying',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 305,
        question: 'Choose the correct form: They regret ____ the party early.',
        options: ['to leave', 'leaving', 'leave'],
        answer: 'leaving',
    },

    // Modal Verbs
    {
        lesson_id: 306,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for probability: She ____ go to the cinema. It ____ be late now.',
        options: ['may / may', 'might / might', 'might / may'],
        answer: 'might / may',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 306,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for polite request: ____ I sit here? ____ I ask you something?',
        options: ['May / May', 'Can / Can', 'Might / Might'],
        answer: 'May / Might',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 306,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for past ability: She ____ have seen me. She ____ have left the purse on the table.',
        options: ["can't / can", "couldn't / can't", "couldn't / can"],
        answer: "couldn't / can't",
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 306,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for polite request: ____ you change my room, please?',
        options: ['Can', 'May', 'Could'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 306,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for probability: We ____ ask her again.',
        options: ['may', 'can', 'should'],
        answer: 'can',
    },

    // Past Tenses
    {
        lesson_id: 307,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: I ____ tired last night.',
        options: ['am', 'was', 'have been'],
        answer: 'was',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 307,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: They ____ in Australia in 2010.',
        options: ['are living', 'were living', 'have been living'],
        answer: 'were living',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 307,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: When I arrived, everybody ____ left.',
        options: ['has', 'had', 'have'],
        answer: 'had',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 307,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: I ____ basketball for two hours before I got tired.',
        options: ['played', 'have been playing', 'had been playing'],
        answer: 'had been playing',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 307,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: I ____ to have a dog when I was a child.',
        options: ['am used to', 'use', 'used'],
        answer: 'used',
    },

    // Prepositions
    {
        lesson_id: 308,
        question:
            'Choose the correct preposition: She lives ____ the city center.',
        options: ['in', 'on', 'at'],
        answer: 'in',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 308,
        question: 'Choose the correct preposition: I will be away ____ a week.',
        options: ['for', 'since', 'from'],
        answer: 'for',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 308,
        question: 'Choose the correct preposition: They traveled ____ Italy.',
        options: ['to', 'from', 'at'],
        answer: 'to',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 308,
        question: 'Choose the correct preposition: The book is ____ the table.',
        options: ['among', 'on', 'at'],
        answer: 'on',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 308,
        question: 'Choose the correct preposition: We met ____ the park.',
        options: ['in', 'until', 'on'],
        answer: 'in',
    },

    // Present Tenses
    {
        lesson_id: 309,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: I ____ from Greece.',
        options: ['come', 'am coming', 'have come'],
        answer: 'come',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 309,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: She ____ right now. Why ____ you wearing a coat?',
        options: [
            "isn't eating / are",
            "doesn't eat / are",
            "doesn't eat / do",
        ],
        answer: "isn't eating / are",
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 309,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: I have never seen that film before. She ____ yet.',
        options: ["hasn't written", "hasn't written", "haven't written"],
        answer: "hasn't written",
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 309,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: I ____ English for years.',
        options: ['have been learning', 'have learned', 'learn'],
        answer: 'have been learning',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 309,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: The book has been rewritten many times. The dinner ____.',
        options: ['is served', 'was served', 'has served'],
        answer: 'is served',
    },

    // Pronouns
    {
        lesson_id: 310,
        question: "Choose the correct pronoun: I don't have ____ to eat.",
        options: ['something', 'anything', 'nothing'],
        answer: 'anything',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 310,
        question:
            'Choose the correct reflexive pronoun: He hurt ____ while playing soccer.',
        options: ['me', 'himself', 'her'],
        answer: 'himself',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 310,
        question:
            'Choose the correct reflexive pronoun: We should be proud of ____ for completing the project.',
        options: ['ourselves', 'myself', 'yourself'],
        answer: 'ourselves',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 310,
        question:
            'Choose the correct pronoun: ____ is waiting for you outside.',
        options: ['Somebody', 'Nobody', 'Everybody'],
        answer: 'Somebody',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 310,
        question: 'Choose the correct pronoun: She can handle it ____.',
        options: ['on', 'by', 'herself'],
        answer: 'herself',
    },
];

const UpperIntermediate: INTF_HomeWork[] = [
    // Adjectives and Adverbs
    {
        lesson_id: 401,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form: I am ____ (interest) in your offer. Your offer is ____ (interest).',
        options: [
            'interested / interesting',
            'interest / interested',
            'interesting / interested',
            'interested / interesting',
        ],
        answer: 'interested / interesting',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 401,
        question:
            'Choose the correct adverb: He ____ (always / sometimes) arrives late.',
        options: ['always', 'sometimes', 'never', 'seldom'],
        answer: 'always',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 401,
        question:
            'Choose the correct word order: I am ____ (late / never). I ____ (people / 10 p.m.) call after 10 p.m.',
        options: [
            'never / never',
            'never / always',
            'late / sometimes',
            'never / sometimes',
        ],
        answer: 'never / never',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 401,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form: This is the ____ (far / further / farthest) place I have ever been to.',
        options: [
            'far / further / farthest',
            'farther / further / farthest',
            'far / further / farther',
            'further / farther / farthest',
        ],
        answer: 'farthest / furthest',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 401,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form: Laura gets ____ (the same / same) salary as me. Youâ€™re just ____ (the same / same) as your mother.',
        options: [
            'the same / the same',
            'the same / same',
            'same / the same',
            'same / same',
        ],
        answer: 'the same / the same',
    },

    // Conditionals
    {
        lesson_id: 402,
        question:
            'Choose the correct conditional: If you are happy, ____ your hands.',
        options: ['clap', 'claps', 'clapped', 'clapping'],
        answer: 'clap',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 402,
        question: 'Choose the correct conditional: If it rains, ____ at home.',
        options: ['I stay', 'I will stay', 'I stayed', 'I staying'],
        answer: 'I will stay',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 402,
        question:
            'Choose the correct conditional: If I ____ you, I would drink more water.',
        options: ['am', 'is', 'were', 'be'],
        answer: 'were',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 402,
        question:
            'Choose the correct conditional: If I had married Paul, I ____ in that beautiful house.',
        options: ['live', 'lived', 'am living', 'will live'],
        answer: 'would have lived',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 402,
        question:
            'Choose the correct conditional: If I had worked harder at school, I ____ a better job now.',
        options: ['have', 'had', 'would have', 'will have'],
        answer: 'would have',
    },

    // Future Tenses
    {
        lesson_id: 403,
        question:
            'Choose the correct future tense: I ____ sure she will win the race.',
        options: ['am', 'is', 'are', 'will'],
        answer: 'am',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 403,
        question:
            'Choose the correct future tense: I ____ taking my nephew to a concert tomorrow.',
        options: ['am', 'is', 'are', 'will be'],
        answer: 'will be',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 403,
        question: 'Choose the correct future tense: I ____ buy some books.',
        options: ['will', 'am', 'are', 'is'],
        answer: 'am going to',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 403,
        question:
            "Choose the correct future tense: I'm sure you ____ the test.",
        options: ['will pass', 'passed', 'pass', 'will passing'],
        answer: 'will pass',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 403,
        question:
            'Choose the correct future tense: I ____ used to living in a city eventually.',
        options: ['will', 'am', 'are', 'is'],
        answer: 'will get',
    },

    // Gerund and Infinitive
    {
        lesson_id: 404,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form: Forming nouns from verbs using ____ (-ing).',
        options: ['-ing', '-ed', '-ly', '-ful'],
        answer: '-ing',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 404,
        question:
            'Choose the verb followed by a gerund: She ____ swimming every morning.',
        options: ['likes', 'like', 'liking', 'liked'],
        answer: 'likes',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 404,
        question:
            'Choose the verb followed by an infinitive: She decided ____ a new car.',
        options: ['buy', 'buying', 'to buy', 'bought'],
        answer: 'to buy',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 404,
        question:
            'Choose the verb followed by a bare infinitive: I ____ go to the party.',
        options: ['rather', 'had better', 'prefer', 'mind'],
        answer: 'had better',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 404,
        question:
            "Choose the verb followed by 'to + gerund': I will help ____ the dishes.",
        options: ['washing', 'wash', 'washed', 'to wash'],
        answer: 'to wash',
    },

    // Modal Verbs
    {
        lesson_id: 405,
        question: 'Choose the modal verb for probability: It ____ rain.',
        options: ['may', 'might', 'can', 'could'],
        answer: 'might',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 405,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for polite request: ____ I see your passport?',
        options: ['May', 'Might', 'Can', 'Could'],
        answer: 'May',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 405,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for deduction or speculation: It ____ look for another job.',
        options: ['may', 'might', 'can', 'could'],
        answer: 'might',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 405,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form: It ____ have been Sarah last night.',
        options: ['can', "can't", 'could', "couldn't"],
        answer: 'could',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 405,
        question:
            'Choose the modal verb for polite request: ____ I see your manager? Could you say it again?',
        options: ['Can', 'Could', 'May', 'Might'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },

    // Past Tenses
    {
        lesson_id: 406,
        question: 'Choose the correct past tense: They ____ TV all evening.',
        options: ['watched', 'watch', 'watches', 'were watching'],
        answer: 'watched',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 406,
        question:
            'Choose the correct past tense: The telephone rang when she ____ a bath.',
        options: ['had', 'has', 'was having', 'had been having'],
        answer: 'was having',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 406,
        question:
            'Choose the correct past tense: She ____ the keys she had lost.',
        options: ['found', 'finds', 'finding', 'had found'],
        answer: 'found',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 406,
        question:
            'Choose the correct past tense: We ____ playing tennis all evening.',
        options: ['had', 'have', 'were', 'had been'],
        answer: 'had been',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 406,
        question: 'Choose the correct form: She ____ play football as a kid.',
        options: ['used', 'was used to', 'used to', 'were used to'],
        answer: 'used to',
    },

    // Prepositions
    {
        lesson_id: 407,
        question:
            'Choose the correct preposition: Prepositional phrases ____ in, for, from, to, at, in, about, with, from, of, etc.',
        options: ['with', 'at', 'for', 'among'],
        answer: 'with',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 407,
        question:
            'Choose the correct preposition: ____ the rain, we decided to stay at home.',
        options: ['Until', 'On', 'In', 'By'],
        answer: 'In',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 407,
        question:
            'Choose the correct preposition: She is worried ____ her test results.',
        options: ['by', 'of', 'about', 'from'],
        answer: 'about',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 407,
        question: 'Choose the correct preposition: The book is ____ the table.',
        options: ['with', 'from', 'to', 'on'],
        answer: 'on',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 407,
        question:
            'Choose the correct preposition: I am going ____ a vacation next week.',
        options: ['with', 'to', 'at', 'from'],
        answer: 'on',
    },

    // Present Tenses
    {
        lesson_id: 408,
        question:
            'Choose the correct present tense: Mark usually ____ football on Sundays.',
        options: ['play', 'playing', 'plays', 'played'],
        answer: 'plays',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 408,
        question:
            'Choose the correct stative verb: I ____ chocolate ice cream.',
        options: ['likes', 'like', 'liking', 'liked'],
        answer: 'like',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 408,
        question:
            'Choose the correct present tense for future: The train ____ at 8.',
        options: ['leaves', 'leave', 'leaving', 'left'],
        answer: 'leaves',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 408,
        question: 'Choose the correct present tense: Please be quiet, I ____.',
        options: ['work', 'am working', 'works', 'worked'],
        answer: 'am working',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 408,
        question:
            'Choose the correct present tense: They ____ to school every day.',
        options: ['go', 'goes', 'going', 'went'],
        answer: 'go',
    },

    // Pronouns
    {
        lesson_id: 409,
        question: 'Choose the correct pronoun: Did you find ____ wallet?',
        options: ['my', 'mine', 'me', 'myself'],
        answer: 'my',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 409,
        question:
            'Choose the correct relative pronoun: The person ____ won the competition received a prize.',
        options: ['which', 'who', 'whose', 'whom'],
        answer: 'who',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 409,
        question:
            'Choose the correct pronoun: They went to the park ____ for a picnic.',
        options: ['some', 'any', 'somewhere', 'anywhere'],
        answer: 'somewhere',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 409,
        question:
            'Choose the correct reflexive pronoun: We did the assignment ____ without any help.',
        options: ['ourselves', 'yourselves', 'themselves', 'myself'],
        answer: 'ourselves',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 409,
        question: 'Choose the correct pronoun: I want ____ to eat.',
        options: ['something', 'anything', 'someone', 'anyone'],
        answer: 'something',
    },
];

const Confident: INTF_HomeWork[] = [
    // Adjectives and Adverbs
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: This is the ____ book I have ever read.',
        options: [
            'interesting',
            'more interesting',
            'most interesting',
            'interestinger',
        ],
        answer: 'most interesting',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb: He speaks English ____.',
        options: ['good', 'better', 'best', 'well'],
        answer: 'well',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: That was ____ film I have ever seen.',
        options: ['boring', 'more boring', 'most boring', 'boringer'],
        answer: 'the most boring',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb: She sings ____.',
        options: ['good', 'better', 'best', 'well'],
        answer: 'well',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: This is a ____ dress than the one I bought last week.',
        options: ['cheap', 'cheaper', 'cheapest', 'cheaperer'],
        answer: 'cheaper',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb: He runs ____.',
        options: ['fast', 'faster', 'fastest', 'fasterer'],
        answer: 'fast',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: She is ____ person I know.',
        options: ['friendly', 'friendlier', 'friendliest', 'friendlierer'],
        answer: 'the friendliest',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb: He plays the piano ____.',
        options: [
            'beautiful',
            'more beautifully',
            'most beautifully',
            'beautifuler',
        ],
        answer: 'beautifully',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: That is ____ car I have ever driven.',
        options: ['fast', 'faster', 'fastest', 'fasterer'],
        answer: 'the fastest',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 501,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb: He speaks French ____.',
        options: ['fluent', 'more fluently', 'most fluently', 'fluenter'],
        answer: 'fluently',
    },

    // Modal Verbs
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: He ____ be at home, I saw him outside.',
        options: ['might', 'should', 'would', 'could'],
        answer: "can't",
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: She ____ have left her keys at the office.',
        options: ['may', 'can', 'must', 'would'],
        answer: 'must',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: They ____ have missed the train.',
        options: ['might', 'should', 'would', 'could'],
        answer: 'could',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: We ____ go swimming tomorrow if the weather is good.',
        options: ['might', 'should', 'would', 'could'],
        answer: 'might',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: You ____ study harder if you want to pass the exam.',
        options: ['may', 'can', 'must', 'should'],
        answer: 'must',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: She ____ be very tired after running a marathon.',
        options: ['may', 'can', 'must', 'should'],
        answer: 'must',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: He ____ have been sleeping when we called him.',
        options: ['may', 'can', 'must', 'would'],
        answer: 'must',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            "Choose the correct modal verb: We ____ arrive late if we don't leave now.",
        options: ['might', 'should', 'would', 'could'],
        answer: 'might',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            "Choose the correct modal verb: You ____ ask permission before using someone else's belongings.",
        options: ['may', 'can', 'must', 'should'],
        answer: 'should',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 502,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: They ____ have seen the accident happen.',
        options: ['might', 'should', 'would', 'could'],
        answer: 'could',
    },

    // Conditionals
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If I ____ a car, I would drive to work.',
        options: ['had', 'have', 'will have', 'would have'],
        answer: 'had',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If it ____ tomorrow, we won't go to the beach.",
        options: ['rains', 'rain', 'will rain', 'would rain'],
        answer: 'rains',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If he ____ her, he would have apologized.',
        options: ['loves', 'love', 'will love', 'had loved'],
        answer: 'loved',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If they ____ a map, they would have found the way.',
        options: ['have', 'has', 'will have', 'had'],
        answer: 'had',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If she ____ earlier, she wouldn't be late now.",
        options: ['leaves', 'leave', 'will leave', 'would leave'],
        answer: 'had left',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If we ____ more money, we could buy a bigger house.',
        options: ['have', 'has', 'will have', 'had'],
        answer: 'had',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If it ____ warmer, we would go for a swim.',
        options: ['is', 'was', 'will be', 'were'],
        answer: 'were',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If he ____ the invitation, he would have missed the party.',
        options: ['accepted', 'accept', 'will accept', 'would accept'],
        answer: 'had accepted',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If they ____ earlier, they would have caught the train.',
        options: ['leave', 'leaves', 'will leave', 'had left'],
        answer: 'had left',
    },
    {
        lesson_id: 503,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If you ____ more effort, you would have succeeded.',
        options: ['put', 'puts', 'will put', 'had put'],
        answer: 'had put',
    },
];

const BeginnerH = Beginner.length / 5;
const PreIntermediateH = PreIntermediate.length / 5;
const IntermediateH = Intermediate.length / 5;
const UpperIntermediateH = UpperIntermediate.length / 5;
const ConfidentH = Confident.length / 10;

export {
    Beginner,
    PreIntermediate,
    Intermediate,
    UpperIntermediate,
    Confident,
    BeginnerH,
    PreIntermediateH,
    IntermediateH,
    UpperIntermediateH,
    ConfidentH,
};
